UTAGE: Unity Text Adventure Game Engine
Trial Version 
Copyright 2014 Ryohei Tokimura

Thank you for buying UTAGE

Support:
Japanese Web Site
http://madnesslabo.net/utage/

English Document
http://madnesslabo.net/utage/?page_id=28



これは宴の体験版です。
内部の評定および/または教育目的だけのために、このバージョンを使用することができます。
非商用であれば、WebPlayerとしてアプリを公開することができます。
ソースコードの再頒布は禁止ですが、教育/レビューの目的でソースコードの一部を公開することは許可します。

This is a UTAGE trial version
You can use this version for internal, evaluational and/or educational purposes only.
If it is non-commercial, you will be able to publish the app as WebPlayer
Redistributions of source code is prohibited, but it is permitted to publish part of the source code for the purpose of education / review.

